Hey, out of all of us, who do you think's going to get married next?
嘿，在我們所有人中，你認為下一個要結婚的是誰？
Probably Monica and Chandler.
可能是莫妮卡和錢德勒。
Hi, could I have a pack of Newport Lights, please?
你好，能給我一包紐波特燈嗎？
Oh, um, we don't sell cigarettes, but they have them at the new stand across the street.
哦，嗯，我們不賣香煙，但他們在街對面的新攤位上有賣。
That'd be great, thanks.
那太好了，謝謝。
Oh, my God, Melissa Warburton, I don't think I have the energy for this.
哦，天哪，梅麗莎·沃伯頓，我想我沒有精力做這件事。
Oh, my God, Ray Ray Green?
哦，天啊，雷·雷·格林？
You have been MIA for the past seven sorority newsletters.
在過去的七份聯誼會時事通訊中，您一直沒有消失。
What's up with you?
你怎麼了？
Why didn't I tell you over here?
我為什麼不在這裡告訴你？
So, last I heard, you were going to get married.
所以，我上次聽說，你要結婚了。
Poor Ray Ray.
可憐的雷雷。
Oh, no, no, no, it's good, it's all good.
噢，不，不，不，很好，一切都很好。
I actually work at Ralph Lauren.
我實際上在拉爾夫·勞倫工作。
Shut up!
住口！
I will not.
我不會。
I am the divisional head of men's sportswear.
我是男士運動服部門的負責人。
Oh, shut up more!
唉，你再閉嘴一點吧！
Are you friends with Ralph?
你和拉爾夫是朋友嗎？
Oh, please.
哦，拜託。
Are you?
你是？
No.
不。
Listen, we have to have dinner.
聽著，我們得吃晚餐了。
What are you doing tomorrow night?
明天晚上你要做什麼？
Oh, tomorrow?
噢，明天？
I don't know.
我不知道。
You do now.
你現在就做。
You're having dinner with me.
你正在和我一起吃晚餐。
Shut up!
住口！
I've got to go.
我得走了。
This has been so great, Ray Ray.
這太棒了，雷雷。
Oh, there you are.
哦，你在那裡。
You're a bad man for giving me these.
你給我這些是個壞人。
So, listen, just call me.
所以，聽著，打電話給我。
Here's my card.
這是我的名片。
Oh, wow, thanks.
哦，哇，謝謝。
Oh, you're in real estate.
哦，你是做房地產的。
Oh, no, that's an old card.
哦，不，那是一張舊卡。
I wanted to get out of that and do something where I could really help people and make
我想擺脫這種困境，做一些真正可以幫助人們並做出貢獻的事情
a difference.
一個區別。
Wow.
哇。
So, what do you do now?
那麼，你現在在做什麼？
I'm a party planner.
我是派對策劃者。
I'll see you tomorrow.
明天見。
Okay.
好的。
Hey, guys, look who's back.
嘿，夥計們，看看誰回來了。
It's Ray Ray.
是雷雷。
That was my friend Melissa from college.
那是我大學時的朋友梅莉莎。
She seems really, really fun.
她看起來真的非常非常有趣。
She's actually very sweet, and we used to be very close.
她其實很可愛，我們曾經很親密。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
She's not the one who you...
她不是你...
Who you what?
你是誰你什麼？
Yes.
是的。
Wow.
哇。
Wow, wow, what?
哇哇哇什麼？
Wow, what?
哇，什麼？
Who you what?
你是誰你什麼？
It's not a big deal.
這沒什麼大不了的。
They were lovers.
他們是戀人。
What?
什麼？
No, we weren't.
不，我們不是。
It was nothing.
沒什麼。
It was one night, senior year, we went to a party, had a lot of sangria, and, you know,
那是高年級的一個晚上，我們去參加一個聚會，喝了很多桑格利亞汽酒，而且，你知道，
ended up kissing for a bit.
最後接吻了一會兒。
So, that's two of my wives.
這是我的兩個妻子。
Where are you going?
你要去哪裡？
To bring her back here.
要把她帶回這裡。
Ross, get the sangria.
羅斯，來一杯桑格利亞汽酒。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Okay, so, this is where the band is, and this is where the bar is, and all these pins
好的，這就是樂隊所在的位置，這是酒吧所在的位置，還有所有這些別針
have people's names on them.
上面有人們的名字。
Oh, Rach, here you are.
哦，瑞秋，你來了。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
Well, why don't we just take me and put me with a Manhattan in my hand, talking to the
好吧，我們為什麼不帶我去，讓我手裡拿著曼哈頓，與
cute bartender?
可愛的調酒師？
These pins aren't for playing, are they?
這些別針不是用來玩的，是嗎？
Okay, the red ones are my guests, and the blue pins are yours.
好的，紅色的別針是我的客人，藍色的別針是你的。
This is so sad.
這太悲傷了。
I mean, I only have, like, ten pins.
我的意思是，我只有十個別針。
Chandler, relax.
錢德勒，放鬆點。
It's not a contest.
這不是一場競賽。
It's certainly not a close one.
這當然不是一個親密的關係。
Hello.
你好。
Hey.
嘿。
Hey, Rach.
嘿，瑞秋。
Stop picturing it.
別再想像了。
Okay, I think that's it.
好吧，我想就是這樣。
The seating chart is done.
座位表已經做好了。
This is our wedding.
這是我們的婚禮。
Wow.
哇。
They all look like they're having fun, don't they?
他們看起來都玩得很開心，不是嗎？
Hey, so, where are my parents going to be?
嘿，那麼，我的父母要去哪裡呢？
Oh.
哦。
Let's see.
讓我們來看看。
Well, if this is the wedding hall, then your parents would be over here at home in Queens.
好吧，如果這是婚禮大廳，那麼你的父母就會在皇后區的家裡。
What?
什麼？
They're not invited?
他們沒有被邀請？
Oh, no.
哦，不。
That's terrible.
太可怕了。
They're going to be crushed.
他們會被壓垮的。
Why would they think they're invited?
為什麼他們會認為自己被邀請了？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
You got me.
你抓住了我。
I don't...
我不...
Joey.
喬伊。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
Look, I thought parents were coming.
瞧，我以為父母會來。
You know, your parents are coming.
你知道，你的父母要來了。
Chandler's parents are coming.
錢德勒的父母來了。
Ross's parents are coming.
羅斯的父母來了。
Ross's parents are my parents.
羅斯的父母就是我的父母。
Well, see?
嗯，看到了嗎？
Parents are coming.
父母來了。
You know, I think we should invite them.
你知道，我認為我們應該邀請他們。
Oh, please.
哦，拜託。
You just want more blue pins.
你只是想要更多的藍色別針。
Well, this is just sad.
嗯，這只是悲傷。
All right.
好的。
Maybe I can fit them in.
也許我可以把他們放進去。
And if I just do some rearranging.
如果我只是做一些重新安排。
But, you know, Rachel may actually have to sit at the bar.
但是，你知道，雷切爾實際上可能不得不坐在酒吧裡。
That is not a problem.
那不是問題。
Maybe you order a little sangria.
也許你點了一點桑格利亞汽酒。
Oh, get out of here!
噢，離開這裡！
So, now, these are all the tuxedos that we make, and if there's anything that you like,
所以，現在，這些都是我們做的燕尾服，如果有什麼你喜歡的，
we can make you a deal.
我們可以與您達成協議。
Anything at all.
任何事情都可以。
But these are the three that Monica pre-approved.
但這是莫妮卡預先批准的三個。
Ah, well, thanks a lot for hooking me up, Rach.
啊，好吧，非常感謝你邀請我，瑞秋。
And I want you to know that I want you to attend our wedding as my guest.
我想讓你知道我希望你作為我的客人參加我們的婚禮。
I'm Monica's maid of honor.
我是莫妮卡的伴娘
Okay?
好的？
Don't try to blue pin me.
不要試圖對我進行藍色固定。
Well, what's the deal with these?
嗯，這些是怎麼回事？
These look nice.
這些看起來不錯。
Oh, they are nice.
哦，他們很好。
We custom make tuxedos for celebrities, and then when they're done with them, they just
我們為名人訂製燕尾服，然後當他們完成後，他們只是
send them back.
把他們送回去。
You mean, like, for award shows?
你是說頒獎典禮？
Some of them.
其中一些。
You mean these tuxedos have been down the red carpet with people yelling, uh, who are
你的意思是這些燕尾服走上紅毯，人們大喊，呃，誰是
you wearing?
你穿嗎？
You look fabulous!
你看起來棒極了！
Honey, might I suggest watching a little more ESPN and a little less E...
親愛的，我可以建議多看一點 ESPN，少看 E...
Okay, who wore those?
好吧，誰穿了這些？
Um, well, it's, uh, this one's Tom Brokaw.
嗯，嗯，這是，呃，這是湯姆·布羅考。
Not bad.
不錯。
This one is, uh, Paul O'Neill.
這個人是，呃，保羅·奧尼爾。
Who's that?
那是誰？
He plays for the Yankees.
他為洋基隊效力。
Seriously, ESPN.
說真的，ESPN。
Just once in a while.
只是偶爾一次。
Have it on in the background.
將其放在後臺。
Ooh, this one was Pierce Brosnan.
哦，這個人是皮爾斯布魯斯南。
Pierce Brosnan?
皮爾斯布洛斯南？
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
Are you serious?
你是認真的？
Doubles.
雙打。
Double of seven?
雙七？
This is James Bond's tux?
這是詹姆士龐德的禮服？
Oh, I have to get married in James Bond's tux.
哦，我必須穿著詹姆斯龐德的禮服結婚。
It's a pretty cool tux.
這是一件非常酷的禮服。
Ah, and not just that.
啊，不僅如此。
I would be England's most powerful weapon.
我將成為英格蘭最強大的武器。
A jet-setting heartbreaker on Her Majesty's Secret Service.
女王陛下特勤局中的一名坐飛機的令人心碎的人。
A man who fears no one with a license to kill.
一個擁有殺人執照的人不畏懼任何人。
Wouldn't mind if you let me wear this?
你不介意讓我穿這個嗎？
We should really learn how to play the real way.
我們真的應該學習如何真正打球。
I like our way.
我喜歡我們的方式。
Oh.
哦。
Hey.
嘿。
Chess!
棋！
Nice move.
不錯的舉動。
Yeah.
是的。
Hey.
嘿。
So, Joey, I just hooked Ross and Chandler up
所以，喬伊，我剛剛把羅斯和錢德勒聯絡起來
with some tuxedos for the wedding.
還有一些婚禮用的燕尾服。
Do you need one?
您需要一個嗎？
No, I'm performing the ceremony.
不，我正在主持儀式。
I'm not wearing a tux.
我沒有穿燕尾服。
Well, what are you going to wear?
嗯，你要穿什麼？
Multi-colored robes.
多色長袍。
Ooh, maybe a hat.
哦，也許是一頂帽子。
Huh.
呵呵。
Does Monica know about this?
莫妮卡知道這件事嗎？
I don't think so.
我不這麼認為。
Can I please be there when you tell her?
你告訴她的時候我可以在場嗎？
Hey, oh, right, sweet.
嘿，哦，對了，親愛的。
Do you want to go to a movie tonight?
今晚想去看電影嗎？
Oh, you know what?
哦，你知道嗎？
I can't.
我不能。
I have to have dinner with that Melissa girl.
我得和那個梅麗莎女孩一起吃晚餐。
Can I come?
我可以來嗎？
I won't even talk.
我甚至不會說話。
You just hear the noise from my video camera.
你只會聽到我的攝影機發出的噪音。
What is this?
這是什麼？
What's going on?
這是怎麼回事？
Oh, good.
哦，很好。
Can I tell it?
我可以告訴它嗎？
Well, do you want to hear what actually happened
好吧，你想聽聽底發生了什麼事嗎？
or Joey's lewd version?
還是喬伊的淫蕩版本？
Joey's.
喬伊的。
Okay.
好的。
Hey, come on.
嘿，來吧。
I had this friend from college,
我有一個大學時期的朋友
and I made the stupid mistake of telling Joey
我犯了一個愚蠢的錯誤告訴喬伊
that one time she and I, you know, kissed a little bit.
有一次她和我，你知道，吻了一下。
Yeah, I'm sure that happened.
是的，我確定那件事發生了。
It did.
確實如此。
Sure.
當然。
Hey, it happened.
嘿，事情發生了。
Yeah, it was senior year in college.
是的，那是大學四年級。
It was after the Sigma Chi Luau,
那是在 Sigma Chi Luau 之後，
and Melissa and I got very drunk,
梅麗莎和我喝得很醉，
and we ended up kissing for several minutes.
最後我們接吻了幾分鐘。
Which means she had a couple spritzers
這意味著她喝了幾杯雪碧
and a quick peck on the cheek.
然後在臉頰上飛快地吻了一下。
Why are you taking this away from me?
為什麼要把這個從我身邊奪走？
Why is this so hard for you to believe?
為什麼這會讓你如此難以相信？
Okay, I just, I didn't know that you were lesbian.
好吧，我只是，我不知道你是女同性戀。
I'm not saying that I am a lesbian.
我並不是說我是女同性戀。
I'm just saying that this happened.
我只是說這件事發生了。
Okay.
好的。
It just seems pretty wild,
看起來很狂野，
and you're, you know, so vanilla.
而你，你知道，很普通。
Vanilla?
香草？
I'm not vanilla.
我不是香草。
I've done lots of crazy things.
我做過很多瘋狂的事。
I mean, I got drunk and married in Vegas.
我是說，我喝醉了，然後在維加斯結婚了。
To Ross.
給羅斯。
All right, you know what?
好吧，你知道嗎？
If you don't want to believe me about this,
如果你不想相信我的話
why don't you just come with me to dinner tonight,
今晚為什麼不跟我一起去吃晚餐呢
and she will tell you.
她會告訴你。
Okay, all right, yeah,
好吧，好吧，是的，
because I just can't picture it.
因為我無法想像它。
Oh, you should get inside my head.
哦，你應該進入我的腦海。
All right.
好的。
Hey, guess what I got for your wedding.
嘿，猜猜我為你的婚禮準備了什麼禮物。
A freakishly thin date with a hanger for a head?
瘦得出奇、頭上有衣架的約會物件？
No, Rachel hooked me up with a tux.
不，雷切爾給我穿上了禮服。
But not just any tux,
但不僅僅是任何禮服，
Batman's tux!
蝙蝠俠的禮服！
What?
什麼？
That's right.
這是正確的。
Made expressly for Val Kilmer,
專為 Val Kilmer 打造，
and worn by him in the hit film,
以及他在熱門電影中所佩戴的，
that Batman film he was in.
他參演的那部蝙蝠俠電影
You can't wear that.
你不能穿那個。
I'm wearing the famous tux,
我穿著著名的禮服，
James Bond's tux.
詹姆士龐德的禮服。
So?
所以？
So, if you wear that,
所以，如果你這麼穿的話，
it'll make mine less special.
它會讓我的變得不那麼特別。
Well, you need something to make this date special?
那麼，您需要一些東西讓這次約會變得特別嗎？
Hello?
你好？
You have the most special thing of all.
你擁有最特別的東西。
You are marrying the woman you love.
你要和你愛的女人結婚了。
Please don't take away my cool thing.
請不要拿走我最酷的東西。
Please, pretty please?
拜託，漂亮嗎？
Pretty please?
請問漂亮嗎？
Not very, uh, 007.
不太，呃，007。
Look, it's my wedding day, okay?
聽著，今天是我的婚禮，好嗎？
If you were getting married,
如果你要結婚的話
I would never do anything to upset you.
我永遠不會做任何讓你不高興的事。
When I got married, you slept with my sister.
我結婚的時候，你和妹妹睡了。
That was pretty 007.
那是相當漂亮的007。
Hey.
嘿。
Hey. Okay, good.
嘿。好的，很好。
You're here.
你在這裡。
All right, I figured it out.
好吧，我想通了。
I'm gonna take two tables of eight,
我要兩桌八人
I'm gonna add your parents,
我要新增你的父母
and I'm gonna turn them into three tables of six, okay?
我要把它們變成三桌，每桌六人，好嗎？
And I called the caterer,
我打電話給餐飲服務商，
I added two extra meals,
我加了兩頓加餐，
we are good to go.
我們可以走了。
Yeah, they're not coming.
是的，他們不會來了。
What?
什麼？
Somehow they got the idea
不知怎的，他們想到了這個主意
that you only invited them because of me.
你只是因為我才邀請他們的。
They feel a little unwanted.
他們感覺有點不受歡迎。
Oh, that's too bad.
哦，那太糟糕了。
It's true, but too bad.
這是真的，但太糟糕了。
Look, Mom, if you could just call my mom.
聽著，媽媽，如果你能打電話給我媽媽就好了。
Oh, Joey.
哦，喬伊。
Come on, look, just tell,
來吧，看看，告訴你，
let her know that you really want them to be there.
讓她知道你真的希望他們在那裡。
Let's not forget, this is a woman
我們不要忘記，這是一個女人
who has sent you many lasagnas over the years.
這些年來他寄了很多烤寬麵條給你。
No, she hasn't.
不，她沒有。
Is it her fault if some of them didn't make it to you?
如果有些人沒能找到你，這是她的錯嗎？
What's it am I gonna say?
我要說什麼？
I don't know, just tell them
我不知道，就告訴他們吧
there was a mix-up with the invitations.
邀請函有誤。
No, no, no, blame it on the post office.
不不不，都怪郵局。
They hate the post office.
他們討厭郵局。
And the Irish.
還有愛爾蘭人。
But I don't think you could blame it on them, so...
但我認為你不能把這歸咎於他們，所以......
Hello?
你好？
Yeah, hi, Mrs. Treviani?
是的，嗨，特雷維亞尼夫人？
Hi, this is Monica Geller.
嗨，這是莫妮卡·蓋勒。
Yeah, I'm just calling to say
是的，我打電話只是想說
that Chandler and I really hope
錢德勒和我真的希望
that you can make it to the wedding.
你可以參加婚禮。
Yeah, apparently a bunch of the invitations that we sent
是的，顯然是我們傳送的一堆邀請
weren't delivered.
沒有交付。
Um, I guess there was some screw-up
嗯，我猜有些搞砸了
at the damn post office.
在該死的郵局。
Tell me about it.
告訴我吧。
Yeah, yeah, the U.S. post office?
是啊是啊，美國郵局？
No, more like U.S. lost office.
不，更像是美國失去了辦公室。
What are they, Irish?
他們是什麼人，愛爾蘭人？
Anyway, his name's Alan,
無論如何，他的名字是艾倫，
and we've been going out for three years.
我們出去已經三年了。
He was my first client when I became a party planner.
當我成為派對策劃者時，他是我的第一個客戶。
He was actually planning a party
他實際上正在策劃一場聚會
for his girlfriend at the time.
為了他當時的女朋友。
Oh, well.
那好吧。
Um, and he was Theta Beta Pi at Syracuse.
嗯，他是錫拉丘茲大學的 Theta Beta Pi。
Oh, oh, that's great.
哦，哦，那太好了。
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
Phoebe, were you ever in a sorority?
菲比，你參加過聯誼會嗎？
Of course, yes.
當然，是的。
I was a, um, Thigh Mega Tampon.
我是一個，呃，大腿巨型衛生棉條。
Love one?
愛一個人嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
You know, we were really huge, too,
你知道，我們也很大，
but then they had to shut us down
但後來他們不得不關閉我們
when Regina Phalange died of alcohol poisoning.
雷吉娜·法蘭吉 (Regina Phalange) 因酒精中毒去世。
Oh, isn't it a shame when one girl
哦，當一個女孩時，這不是一種恥辱嗎？
ruins it with a whole bunch?
用一大堆毀掉它？
Mm, mm-hmm, mm.
嗯，嗯，嗯，嗯。
Anyway, speaking of drinking too much,
無論如何，說到喝太多，
I was, uh, telling Phoebe about that one crazy night
我，呃，告訴菲比那個瘋狂的夜晚
after the Sigma Chi luau where you and I, uh,
在你和我的 Sigma Chi luau 之後，呃，
we made out.
我們做出來了。
What?
什麼？
Remember?
記住？
We, come on, we bought, we had the sarongs on,
我們，來吧，我們買了，我們穿上了紗籠，
and we had the, the coconut bikini tops.
我們有椰子比基尼上衣。
Yeah.
是的。
We went back to the house, and we got really silly,
我們回到家，我們真的傻了，
and we made out.
我們親熱了。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
Ray, Ray, I, I have no idea what you're talking about.
雷，雷，我，我不知道你在說什麼。
Really?
真的嗎？
Ross is Batman.
羅斯是蝙蝠俠。
Well, he did manage to keep his identity secret
好吧，他確實設法保守了自己的身份秘密
for a long time.
許久。
Rachel got Ross the tuxedo
瑞秋給羅斯穿上燕尾服
that Val Kilmer wore in Batman.
瓦爾·基爾默在《蝙蝠俠》中穿的那件衣服。
Okay, Batman is so much cooler than James Bond.
好吧，蝙蝠俠比詹姆士龐德酷多了。
What are you talking about?
你在說什麼？
007 has all those gadgets.
007 擁有所有這些小玩意。
Batman has a utility belt.
蝙蝠俠有一條實用腰帶。
007 has a fancy car.
007有一輛豪華汽車。
Batman has the Batmobile.
蝙蝠俠擁有蝙蝠車。
007 gets all the ladies.
007得到了所有女士的青睞。
Batman has Robin.
蝙蝠俠有羅賓。
ESPN.
ESPN。
We get ESPN, right?
我們有 ESPN，對吧？
How about you go put on your 007 tuxedo,
你去穿上你的007燕尾服怎麼樣？
and I'll make you a nice martini?
我會給你一杯美味的馬丁尼？
Actually, I don't like martinis.
事實上，我不喜歡馬丁尼。
Well, how about a yoo-hoo with the funny straw?
嗯，用有趣的吸管來玩一下喲嗬怎麼樣？
Ooh, yum!
哦，嗯！
Hey.
嘿。
Listen, I know the invitation says 6 o'clock,
聽著，我知道邀請函上寫的是六點鐘，
but does that mean you want people to get there at 6,
但這是否意味著你希望人們 6 點到達那裡，
or the show's gonna start right at 6?
或者演出會在六點開始？
The show.
演出。
Right.
正確的。
The wedding.
婚禮。
Gotcha.
明白了。
But, I mean, it's gonna start a little late, right?
但是，我的意思是，這會開始得有點晚，對吧？
I mean, weddings start late, right?
我的意思是，婚禮開始得很晚，對嗎？
Have you ever been to one of my weddings?
你參加過我的一場婚禮嗎？
Ah, yeah.
啊，是的。
Well, look, the thing is,
嗯，看，事情是，
it's the same day as my niece's christening,
那天是我姪女的洗禮
and I really want my parents to be there in time to see me,
我真的希望我的父母能夠及時趕到現場來看我，
because my part's just in the beginning.
因為我的部分才剛開始。
I'm not even in the rest of the show.
我什至沒有參加演出的其餘部分。
Wedding.
婚禮。
The wedding starts at 6.
婚禮六點開始。
Okay, okay, I totally hear you.
好吧，好吧，我完全聽到了。
Ooh, how about this?
哦，這個怎麼樣？
I vamp a little till they get there.
我稍微踩了一下直到他們到達那裡。
You'll vamp?
你會吸鞋嗎？
Yeah, yeah, you know, I'll, like, warm up the crowd,
是的，是的，你知道，我會，就像，溫暖人群，
ask them where they're from.
問他們來自哪裡。
Because in Joey Tribbiani, you get a minister
因為喬伊·崔比亞尼是牧師
and you get an entertainer.
然後你就會得到一個藝人。
I'm a ministainer.
我是迷你服務生。
There is no one better.
沒有人比他更好了。
There's no one greater.
沒有人比他更偉大了。
Huh?
啊？
Oh, please, God, don't vamp.
哦，上帝啊，求求你別再欺負人了。
Oh, okay, well, maybe, maybe I talk to Chandler.
哦，好吧，好吧，也許，也許我會和錢德勒談談。
Maybe he'd like to get married at 007 o'clock.
也許他想在007點結婚。
All right, all right.
好吧，好吧。
I will give you ten extra minutes.
我再給你十分鐘。
Ten, that is it.
十個，就是這樣。
Oh, that's great. Thank you so much.
哦，那太好了。太感謝了。
All right.
好的。
Well, we're in luck.
好吧，我們很幸運。
Your tux fits perfectly.
你的禮服非常合身。
Chandler, that jacket, it's way too big.
錢德勒，那件夾克太大了。
Oh, that's okay.
哦，沒關係。
The pants are way too small.
褲子太小了。
Thank you.
謝謝。
I'm sorry, sweetie, you cannot wear that.
對不起，親愛的，你不能穿那個。
Now, this means Ross is going to be the only cool one.
現在，這意味著羅斯將成為唯一一個很酷的人。
Something, by the way, I never thought I would say.
順便說一句，我從來沒想過我會說出來。
Dude, take that thing off.
夥計，把那個東西拿掉吧。
You look like a fool.
你看起來像個傻瓜。
Now, come on, come next door with me.
現在，來吧，跟我到隔壁去吧。
I got some minister headdresses I want you to take a look at.
我有一些部長的頭飾想讓你看看。
How can you not remember us kissing?
你怎麼不記得我們接吻了？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I don't remember a lot of things that never happened.
我不記得很多從未發生過的事。
Come on, remember we were on the sleeping porch.
來吧，記住我們在睡覺的門廊上。
We couldn't stop giggling.
我們忍不住咯咯地笑。
And our coconuts kept knocking together.
我們的椰子一直敲在一起。
Oh, somewhere Joey's head is exploding.
哦，喬伊的頭在某個地方爆炸了。
Come on, listen, I'm sorry.
來吧，聽著，對不起。
I don't want to make you uncomfortable,
我不想讓你不舒服
but I told Phoebe that it happened,
但我告訴菲比這件事發生了
and she doesn't believe me.
她不相信我。
I'm sorry, Ray Ray.
對不起，雷雷。
I mean, if I thought it happened, I would say it.
我的意思是，如果我認為這件事發生了，我就會說出來。
Maybe I passed out,
也許我昏倒了，
and you did stuff to me while I was sleeping.
你趁我睡覺的時候對我做了事。
No!
不！
Right.
正確的。
Okay, fine.
好吧，好吧。
You don't have to admit it.
你不必承認這一點。
Because I know that it happened.
因為我知道它發生了。
Okay.
好的。
No, you have to admit it.
不，你必須承認這一點。
We kissed.
我們接吻了。
Say it.
說吧。
Rachel, it's okay.
雷切爾，沒關係。
You don't have to do this, all right?
你不必這樣做，好嗎？
I believe you.
我相信你。
Okay, if you say that you kissed Melissa,
好吧，如果你說你吻了梅麗莎，
then you kissed Melissa.
然後你吻了梅麗莎。
Thank you, Phoebe.
謝謝你，菲比。
Okay.
好的。
She didn't.
她沒有。
I know.
我知道。
Hey.
嘿。
Did you just carry that around?
你剛剛帶著它嗎？
Yes.
是的。
I find it to be something of a conversation piece.
我發現它是一個談話片段。
Between you and...
你和...之間
Gunther.
岡瑟.
Hey, hey, why don't we put them on?
嘿，嘿，我們為什麼不穿上它們呢？
You know, get a picture of Batman and James Bond together.
你知道，拍一張蝙蝠俠和詹姆士龐德在一起的照片。
I would, but mine doesn't fit.
我願意，但我的不適合。
The pants are a little tight.
褲子有點緊。
A little tight?
有點緊？
I can see 00 and 7 in those things.
我可以在那些東西中看到 00 和 7。
Well, that stinks.
嗯，那很臭。
I was looking forward to us wearing our celebrity tuxes together.
我很期待我們一起穿著名人禮服。
Does that mean you're not going to be wearing yours?
這是否意味著你不會穿你的衣服？
What, are you kidding?
什麼，你在開玩笑嗎？
It's Batman's tux!
這是蝙蝠俠的禮服！
Let me try it on.
讓我試戴一下。
Okay, but just the jacket.
好吧，但只是夾克。
00 and 7 are not getting in there.
00 和 7 進不去。
Okay.
好的。
Holy double-vented comfort, Batman.
神聖的雙通風口舒適感，蝙蝠俠。
What's this?
這是什麼？
Huh?
啊？
An invitation to the At First Sight premiere?
《一見鍾情》首映式的邀請函？
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Val Kilmer didn't wear this in Batman.
瓦爾·基爾默在《蝙蝠俠》中沒有穿這件衣服。
He wore it to the premiere of some tutti-frutti love story
他穿著它參加了一些水果愛情故事的首映式
where he played a blind guy.
他在那裡扮演一個盲人。
Let me see that.
讓我看看。
Oh, man.
哦，夥計。
The only superpower you have
你唯一擁有的超能力
is a slightly heightened sense of smell.
是嗅覺稍微增強。
Hey, Monica, Chandler, can I talk to you guys for a second?
嘿，莫妮卡，錢德勒，我可以跟你們聊聊嗎？
All right, that's it. I give up.
好吧，就是這樣。我放棄。
Whatever you want, you can have it.
無論你想要什麼，你都可以擁有。
You want to sing a song, you want to do a dance,
你想唱歌，你想跳舞，
you want your mom to stand at the altar and scream racial slurs,
你希望媽媽站在祭壇前尖叫種族歧視，
I don't care.
我不在乎。
No, no, I just want to thank you guys
不不不，我只是想謝謝你們
for what you did for my parents.
感謝你為我父母所做的一切。
That was really sweet.
那真是太甜蜜了。
They're so happy they get to be a part of your special day.
他們很高興能夠成為您特殊日子的一部分。
Oh.
哦。
Well, you're welcome.
好吧，不客氣。
And tell them we're really glad they're coming.
並告訴他們我們真的很高興他們能來。
Okay, I will.
好的，我會的。
Oh, check out what they got me to wear for the ceremony.
哦，看看他們讓我在儀式上穿什麼。
Huh?
啊？
I wear it like this when I marry you guys,
我結婚的時候就這麼穿
and then this is for party time.
然後這是聚會時間。
It happened.
它發生了。
I am telling you, it happened.
我告訴你，它發生了。
Hey.
嘿。
It was great meeting you.
很高興見到你。
And, uh, Rachel, I don't think I'll be calling you
而且，呃，Rachel，我想我不會打電話給你
because, um, you know, you've got me weird.
因為，嗯，你知道，你讓我很奇怪。
Take care, you guys.
保重，你們。
What? Wait a minute.
什麼？等一下。
No, wait a minute.
不，等一下。
Okay, look, that night was the one wild thing
好吧，聽著，那天晚上是一件瘋狂的事情
I have ever done in my entire life,
我這輩子做過的事
and I'm not going to let you take that away from me.
我不會讓你把它從我身邊奪走。
Okay, so if you don't remember that,
好吧，如果你不記得了，
maybe you will remember this.
也許你會記得這一點。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
You love me.
你愛我。
What?
什麼？
Of course I remember our kiss.
我當然記得我們的吻。
I think about it all the time.
我一直在想這個問題。
I can still hear the coconuts knocking together.
我仍然能聽到椰子碰撞的聲音。
I...
我...
I just didn't want to tell you
我只是不想告訴你
because I didn't think you'd return my love,
因為我沒想到你會回報我的愛
and now that you have...
現在你已經...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇，哇，哇，哇，哇，哇，哇。
Oh, look who's being suddenly shy.
哦，看看誰突然害羞了。
You can't tell me you don't feel what I feel.
你不能告訴我你沒有感受到我的感受。
Nobody can kiss that good.
沒有人能接吻那麼好。
I mean it.
我是認真的。
I'm just... I'm just a good kisser.
我只是……我只是個接吻高手。
Shut up.
住口。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
Oh, you don't have to be sorry.
哦，你不必感到抱歉。
I'm... I'm obviously kidding.
我……我顯然是在開玩笑。
I'm not in love with you.
我不愛你。
I'm in love with her.
我愛上了她。
I don't hear coconuts banging together.
我沒有聽到椰子碰撞的聲音。
I mean, I don't picture your face
我的意思是，我無法想像你的臉
when I make love to my boyfriend.
當我和男友做愛的時候。
Anyway, I gotta go.
無論如何，我得走了。
A kiss goodbye?
吻別？
No? Okay.
不？好的。
Wow.
哇。
I mean, I had no idea that that was...
我的意思是，我不知道那是...
What the hell was that?
那到底是什麼？
Just wanted to see what all the fuss was about.
只是想看看到底有什麼好大驚小怪的。
And?
和？
I thought better.
我想更好了。
All right, I found one that fits.
好吧，我找到合適的了。
Well, you know what they say,
嗯，你知道他們說什麼，
23rd time's a charm.
第23次真是太棒了。
Oh, look at you all handsome.
呵呵，看你們都很帥。
Whose is it?
它是誰的？
Oh, does it matter?
哦，有關係嗎？
All that matters is that you look so handsome.
重要的是你看起來很帥。
Whose is it?
它是誰的？
I don't want to say.
我不想說。
Oh, come on, I don't care.
哦，得了吧，我不在乎。
Come on, whose is it?
來吧，這是誰的？
Diane Keaton.
黛安基頓。